const quizQuestion = [
    {
        question: " What is the name of Han Solo's Ship? ",
        choices: ["C3PO", "Star Destroyer", "Millennium Falcon", "Death Star"],
        correctAnswer: "Millennium Falcon"

    },
    {
        question: " What is the famous weapon used by Jedi Knights in the Star Wars series? ",
        choices: ["Lasers", "Light Saber", "Droids", "Swords"],
        correctAnswer: "Light Saber"

    },
    {
        question: " Which young Jedi Knight becomes Darth Vader? ",
        choices: ["Obi-Wan Kenobi", "Qui-Gon Jin", "Anakin Skywalker", "Han Solo"],
        correctAnswer: "Anakin Skywalker"

    },
    {
        question: " What planet is home to Chewbacca and the Wookiees? ",
        choices: ["Kashyyyk", "Naboo", "Tatooine", "Yavin 4"],
        correctAnswer: "Kashyyyk"

    },
    {
        question: " Who is Luke and Leia's mother?",
        choices: ["Rey", "Ahsoka", "Aayla", "Padme"],
        correctAnswer: "Padme"

    },
    {
        question: " What kind of armor does Boba Fett wear?",
        choices: ["Wookie", "Clone", "Mandalorian", "None"],
        correctAnswer: "Mandalorian"

    },
    {
        question: " Do or do not, there is no ______ - Yoda",
        choices: ["Try", "Stopping", "Quitting", "Practice"],
        correctAnswer: "Try"

    },
    {
        question: " May the ____ be with you",
        choices: ["Gods", "Force", "Jedi's", "Stars"],
        correctAnswer: "Force"

    },
    {
        question: " What are the masters of the 'Dark Side' Called? ",
        choices: ["Dark Masters", "Aliens", "Sith", "Rebels"],
        correctAnswer: "Sith"

    },
    {
        question: " Who is the famous (and very ugly) Bount Hunter? ",
        choices: ["Jaba the Hutt", "Luke", "Dooku", "Ewok"],
        correctAnswer: "Jaba the Hutt"

    },

];

const yesImage = [
    "assets/images/yes.webp",
    "assets/images/yes2.webp"
];

const oopsImage = [
    "assets/images/oops.webp",
    "assets/images/oops2.webp"
]

